A Guide to the Winrock International records FA1739
Rockefeller Archive Center
Winrock International records.
1988, 1990-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Winrock International
FA1739
12 Bound Volumes 12 bound volumes
Imprint
Petit Jean Mountain, AR, WIIAD
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Chronological
Scope and Contents
Collection contains annual reports.
Philanthropists; Agricultural development projects -- Southeast Asia
- Winrock International Annual Reports, 1988, 1990-2000; 1
  Annual reports
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1988 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1988)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1990 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1990)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1991 (Item REF 61.3 WIN 1991)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1992 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1992)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1993 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1993)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1993 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1993)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1994 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1994)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1995 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1995)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1996 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1996)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1997 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1997)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1998 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1998)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 1999 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 1999)
  - Winrock International Annual Report 2000 (Item REF 631.3 WIN 2000)